Hi my name is Jaden and today
I'm here with Cindy one of my
clients she owns a surrogacy agency and
today I'm just gonna ask her a
couple questions to see how it's been
to work with me and the experience
so what is the experience been like and
what have you learned so far that
you didn't know before starting your business
my experience has been great with you obviously like
diving into starting my business was hard
stressful I didn't know what to expect where
to start and from our initial consultation
meeting in person we were literally together
for like six hours and I feel
like I just kind of grounded me and
you helped me figure out what was
gonna be step one to what was
gonna be step 10 of like starting
my business what I needed to focus
my time on I'm so it was nice to
have a timeline but also you helping
me with the marketing and guiding me
Supporting me being there physically video and
emails was a lot of help so so far
it's been amazing I loved working with
you and just like just
from the Meta ads to even just
business stuff in general what is something
that you learned about marketing that you
didn't know before and that has helped
you so much with marketing your own
business honestly I
obviously have some marketing experience but I feel
like you helping me with the Meta ads
I didn't know what you taught me
about the campaigns adding the Meta assets
there you go so I feel like
learning how to like navigate those and
what type of ad we wanna add
to catch the viewers attention like that
is something I had no idea like
what to focus So everything
you help me from the beginning to
the end it literally was amazing and
yeah I think you've taught me a lot
in this industry awesome and so far
from running your Meta I mean what
what success have you seen and and
just like in general like have you
seen a lot of growth in your business and
how's it looking how's the path looking
moving forward so I think it's been about
a month that we started at ads and
I've received over like 2
00 leads so it's a ton and
yeah my business has grown because of
the leads coming in and they're good
quality leads they're coming in every single
day and I'm sorry what was your
other question and where do you see your
business just like based off of what
we've done so far and what I've
done For you like where do you
see the path going now with your
business I think it's growing tremendously just the month
I have a bunch of partnerships clients
you know people applying to become surrogate
so it's grown tremendously and I see
myself you know making three digit numbers
by next year for sure and that's
the whole entire goal that was my
entire goal when we first came into
this she literally told me that she
she wanted to do this for her
family she wanted to do this to
to make more money for her family
and provide for her family and my
goal was to get her to her
goals and make sure that I'm there
with her from the beginning to where
she's thriving with her business and I
mean yeah I mean I think you
so much for you trusting in me and working
with me looking
into Being Meta ads he does it all
he's you know one shop stop so reach
out to Jaden